Huh?
What's this? Did he wet himself?
Prince Lyle?!
I-I didn't!
But that looks like...
Like you have...
I told you I didn't!
Come!
Yes, Your Highness!
Look, it's Prince Lyle.
He's scary.
Mr. Lyle, please walk quietly in the hallway—
Shut it!
Every single one of them!
Why did Prince Lyle stand in front of
us in such wild manner without trying
to hide his ferocious violence?
Don't say it like you encountered a monster.
Probably to keep me in check.
In check?
He's the sixth prince,
and I'm the ninth princess.
In the royal hierarchy, I'm below him.
However, I'm engaged to you,
the Hero's Scar and a sorcerer.
So my status is rapidly rising.
Is that so?
Yes.
And now you've made
your debut into society.
From now on, our status will
be above him in high society.
Sounds complicated.
But with or without Father's order
and our status in high society,
I am happy to be betrothed to you.
As am I.
Next time I meet with the king,
I might kneel in gratitude.
Not that I'd ever do that to a man.
Well, you're supposed to.
For now, I'd like to go
apologize to Prince Lyle.
Don't you dare.
GRADUATION, AND WHAT'S NEXT?
Today is your final exam?
Yes. I only need to go in the afternoon.
A-ori.
For today's alteration,
let's try changing the sensation.
Okay.
This feels like an apple.
Try touching other things
and expressing their sensation.
Yes, Miss Jenié.
What are you working on now?
Collecting samples for alterations.
Right. I don't get it, but okay.
Hello!
Kunon and Master Ixio!
Hello, Your Highness.
Thinking about how today's my last
day to hear your voice at school...
It feels like the world is
fading into dusk out of sorrow.
But school ends in the evening.
Oh, then I'm not sad.
These two really are something else.
You will take the final exam
with the other students.
This feels like an actual school!
But what a shame I'm no longer in a
special room with you, Professor Kast.
I am watching you, even if we have many
other students, so best of luck to you.
You two seem very close now.
We talked a lot during the exams.
During the exams?
Like how she became a teacher,
following a man she was in love with
to the senior school for nobles.
I was young.
But he failed the test and only she
became a teacher. It's her second year.
What the heck am I doing, right?
Professor...
Why would she discuss that with a child?
During the exam, no less?!
Excuse me, Princess Mirika.
Would you please introduce
your fiancé to us?
Introduce him to us, Ixio!
How adorable!
He seems smarter than Ixio, no?
Mr. Kunon, please introduce yourself.
Nice to meet you.
My name is Kunon Gurion.
I'm engaged to Princess Mirika Hughlia,
and I am Ixio Gurion's little brother.
I'm actually relieved right now.
I was starting to wonder if Mirika
and my brother had no friends,
because no one would
approach and talk to them.
I'll let it slide, but don't
disrespect Her Highness.
Indeed! That was because...
I asked them to leave us alone, since
this was a rare opportunity for me
to enjoy my school life with you.
I had no idea!
I appreciate your thoughtfulness,
Your Highness.
Sure.
But it is true that I was worried.
It'd be rude to ask, "Don't you have
friends?" or "Are you usually alone?"
I'm glad that my brother isn't lonely.
I'm really glad Your Highness has friends.
I'm so happy I didn't have to console you
by reminding you of my situation and
saying, "It's fine not to have friends."
Kunon.
You totally are fine not
having friends, aren't you?
Yes.
Humans do surprisingly okay being alone.
I knew you'd say that, Kunon.
Prince Lyle, it's time for the exam.
Professors can wait.
The final exam will be conducted all at once.
I'm afraid even Your Highness
isn't allowed to be late.
M-Maybe that's the case, that is.
Everyone, please take your seats.
Yes, ma'am.
Kunon, your seat is right here.
Hey, Mirika!
Brother Lyle.
I hear he caused trouble at school again.
Apparently, imperial studies couldn't
be extended to the sixth prince.
He is still a prince.
Try to be respectful.
Mr. Lyle, you need to—
Every single one of them...
They can't say anything to my face
but talk behind my back.
They piss me off.
The people at the castle and at this school!
Nice to meet you!
I'm Kunon Gurion, Princess Mirika's fiancé.
Kunon?
Oh, I'm so happy to get
a chance to say hello!
I didn't really get to the other day.
What are you?! What are you?!
Come on now, I'm your future brother-in-law.
Stop messing with me! Let go!
His grip is strong!
He's like a soft-shelled turtle!
Though I've never seen one!
First of all, I never gave you
permission to speak or hold my hand!
Oh, what a manly voice you have.
And I can tell from the feel
that your face must also be manly.
If only my eyes could see, I would have
stared a hole through your manly face!
You...
H-Hey, Mirika! What's wrong with him?
What's wrong with him?!
Brother Lyle.
Why are you laughing?!
I'm sorry.
I never knew that you could get flustered
and blush like that, Big Brother.
I-I'm not blushing!
You! You need to let me go already!
Oh! You're strong, too!
Okay! Enough already!
I'm glad you understand!
Thank you very much!
Would you look at that?
Okay, everyone, take your seats.
I will announce those
who passed the final exam.
All of you passed.
You did it, Prince Lyle!
I'm happy for you.
Thank you, and likewise.
We're graduating together, Kunon.
Congratulations, Your Highness.
I had a great time thanks to
Your Highness and the ladies!
I hope our paths will cross again!
See you, Kunon!
He was a bit quirky, but a
bright, wonderful student.
If you're looking for a boyfriend,
how about my brother?
Then we'll see each
other again in no time!
Kunon, stop that.
I've said too much.
And I've had my heart broken
by a graduate for no reason!
Hmph.
Let's go.
Yes, Your Highness!
We'll come with you wherever you go!
Whirlpool!
Okay. A-ori!
Make a sudden stop and split it into ten!
Yes, ma'am!
Color them red, blue, and green!
Change the texture!
Yes, ma'am!
Very good. Excellent work.
Oh, just a minute.
I've made alterations by adding shape
and temperature to the texture.
What?!
It's over.
What did you want to talk about?
If it's about the dinner
to celebrate graduation,
as a gentleman, I'd love a chance to ask you.
It's not about that,
but your graduation does give me a perfect
opportunity to tell you the truth.
The truth?
Are you mentally prepared?
I'm going to reveal a shocking truth now.
Iko.
No way...
This is so sudden, I can't accept...
that you're actually
the goddess of the night sky
and you must return to
the world of gods soon!
Personally, I love that story,
but that's not it.
The truth is that there is
nothing I can teach you anymore.
What?
I'll stop my poor pretense and come clean.
It's actually been quite a while that
I've had nothing else to teach you.
Elementary magic with no attacking ability...
I've taught everything I could in that range.
Now you're using magic better than I am.
Once you learn new magic,
you will surpass me in no time.
That's not true!
I loved the little magic
tricks you've come up with,
trying to deceive me with every possible method!
Oh, so you were aware that I was desperate.
That makes things easier.
Yes! Your tricks out of desperation
definitely broadened my range of magic!
It's a water spell, "A-ori."
You're producing water using magic.
It's about... the size of an eyeball.
Miss Jenié, you're the one
who gave me a purpose in life.
Master Kunon.
And it was your little tricks that
taught me the depths of magic!
If you truly feel that way,
maybe stop calling them "little tricks."
And I had to rack my brain to squeeze them out.
There were many times I
struggled to come up with one.
That's not true.
It is true.
Because I'm telling you it's true.
Is the problem your salary?
Do you want to quit because the pay is low?
I can ask Father to give you a raise!
Actually, it's the opposite!
It's unbearable to get paid so much
when I have no job to fulfill!
You were getting paid by drawing it out,
so why would you say something like that?!
I'm saying I've hit my limit!
Master Kunon.
You should have an exceptional sorcerer
who's much better than me as your teacher.
I can't help you improve any further.
I can't guide you.
I've managed to make it work with
your lessons, but it's over now.
Even if they're little tricks,
if you can think up so many of them,
then it's a respectable talent.
Deceive me.
Deceive me more!
Deceive me more elegantly!
I want you as my teacher!
Just make it work and deceive me!
I can't do it anymore.
Master Kunon, your magic is far
more advanced than mine now.
No. I like your little tricks!
If you truly like them, stop calling them that!
Never again!
No!
An unmistakable genius.
Maybe Master Kunon has what it takes
to become the Cerulean Sorcerer.
Even Master Kunon, with god-given talents,
went through endless trial and error
and challenged himself to overcome it all.
I can't lose to my pupil.
It's not too late for me either!
What? Lady Flora resigned, too?
Yes. You've finished the curriculum and
officially graduated from the
school for noble children.
But I didn't say goodbye.
She said she wouldn't be able to hold
back tears to say goodbye in person.
Okay. Maybe I'll write a letter of thanks.
Yes, I'm sure she would love
that. While you're at it,
can you ask if there's a male servant
who's between 18 and 25 years old,
well-paid, tall, and
good-looking in her manor?
Your groom-to-be?
Yes!
You'd leave me and get married?
It pains me to be parted
from you, Master Kunon.
But I'd like to get married.
Plus, you'll be perfectly
fine on your own now.
I won't be.
Miss Jenié left me, Lady Flora
left me, and if you leave me, too...
There's an old wives' tale that a
bunny dies when it feels too lonely.
Master Kunon.
I won't ask about a male servant
who's between 18 and 25 years old,
well-paid, tall, and good-looking.
Is that what Miss Jenié said?
Yes. She told me to find an
exceptional sorcerer for my teacher.
An exceptional sorcerer.
Do you have someone in mind, Big Brother?
I heard a rumor at school that there's
an extraordinary Royal Sorcerer.
Royal Sorcerer.
Hold on a minute.
Girls especially were making a
fuss about Zeo-someone or other.
Was it perhaps Master Zeonly Finroll?
That's right!
Apparently he's a sorcerer
of immense power and beauty.
Then I'd like him to be my teacher.
I said hold on!
It's impossible to invite a Royal Sorcerer here.
It is? Even for you, who's favored by and
collusively connected with His Majesty?
Who's feeding you these things?
Is it Iko? It's her, isn't it?
Royal Sorcerer also refers to
a title within the royal court.
Other than His Majesty and those
under his chain of chain of command,
no one can give orders to them.
That's quite strict.
They rarely leave the castle.
Outside of royalty, getting in
touch with them is also restricted.
So meeting him directly is difficult,
let alone inviting him here.
That is correct.
Then how about I accompany you
when you visit the castle,
BY SOME MEANS OR ANOTHER
by some means or another,
and when I'm lost, the Royal Sorcerers
who happen to be there helps me.
And by some means or another
I become their apprentice?
BY SOME MEANS OR ANOTHER
How can you present such a vague,
flawed plan so confidently?
Oh, no. It's an elaborate plan
with a 90% success rate.
The success rate is less than 10%,
and you'd never use "by some means
or another" in an elaborate plan.
Definitely not twice!
I thought it was perfect.
Right, Mother?
AWW
Oh!
Yes, Kunon is perfect.
Mother indulges Kunon.
Listen, my dear.
Can't you do something?
Kunon's practically begging you.
Fine! I will at least ask His Majesty.
And Father indulges Mother.
Thank you very much, Father!
Asking is all I'll do.
Don't get your hopes up.
Dear...
Leave it to me!
I'll make it happen!
Grand Master, I brought you the document.
About that child?
An apprentice-level sorcerer asking to
study under a Royal Sorcerer is unheard of.
Even for a noble close to His Majesty.
Power and status mean
nothing to Royal Sorcerers.
But my little sister Mirika is head
over heels for this tiny sorcerer.
Oh?
Oh?!
Oh!
Kunon Gurion...!
Next episode: "Off to the Castle."
NEXT EPISODE: OFF TO THE CASTLE